Thank you for watching!
Thank you for all your hard work.
This time on Haloste, we have Ria Matsunaga from Juice Juice and
and Mifu Kawashima from Juice Juice.
This time, we're going to show you the two of them, so please stay with us until the end.
Thank you very much.
Now, Mifu Kawashima, this is your first time to be an MC for Haloste, so please introduce yourself.
I'm 16 years old and a sophomore in high school from Kyoto.
My hobby is listening to music.
Pleased to meet you.
Yes, nice to meet you.
So it's been a year since you joined us.
Do you have any experience in the group that you feel “This is JUICE JUICE”?
When I joined JUICE JUICE, I was so surprised to know that there is such a close group.
We get along really well and everyone is like friends.
It's funny.
I think it's really great that everyone respects each other so much.
Indeed, my impression of Mifuyu Kawashima is that she is like a sister to me.
She is like a younger sister to me, partly because we are from the Kansai region.
We are from the same Kansai region, but I think we have a lot of similarities at the core, so she really is like a younger sister to me.
I love the way we sing together in unison, so in a good way it doesn't feel like it's only been a year since we joined the band.
I love the chemistry of unison when we sing together, so in a good way it doesn't feel like it's only been a year since we joined the group.
I think we got used to each other very quickly.
I think we all fit in very quickly.
When I was a trainee, most of the members were from Kanto, not Kansai, so I couldn't speak Kansai dialect very well, but since I joined Juice Juice, I feel like I'm at school now.
It's really lively backstage, and there are a lot of energetic members, so no matter where you come from in the Kansai-Kanto region, you can talk to each other in many different languages.
It's a really lively backstage, and the members are very energetic, so it doesn't matter if you're in the Kansai or Kanto region, everyone is talking to each other in various languages.
Please continue to look forward to the activities of Juice Juice.
Here it is!
I didn't think about it at all, but it turned out to be a short film, and it's very funny.
Quietly 갔 witch Hot ils e printed
It would be obvious if we could find an extra.
This weekend.
I wonder if I can tell someone.
Don't make a weak maiden cry
I'll keep my mouth shut, no automatic queue at all.
Keep it over.
Thank you for watching Thank you for watching!
Yeah, I'm up
Come on, let's dance. Come on, let's get it off your chest.
Yeah, that's a start.
Someday you'll get there.
We can do it again tomorrow. We can do it again tomorrow.
I don't care if you're irresponsible, I don't care how hard you try.
Don't get all mushy, don't slip, don't slip.
Don't spill it. Come here. Go!
Go!
I'll change the times
I knew something good would come out of it
I'm in a good mood
One day I'll get it done.
I can do it again tomorrow
I don't care if I'm irresponsible, I don't care how I try
Don't get all mushy, don't slip, don't spill.
Don't spill it. Come here. Go!
Go!
I'll change the times
I knew something good would come out of it
I'm in a good mood
Oh, yeah!
شكرا!
It's over in three volumes!
The reason for this one...
I ended up helping him, didn't I?
Let's do our best again tomorrow!
With Juice Juice's Riai Matsunaga
Mifu Kawashima of Juice Riai Matsunaga and Mifu Kawashima of Haloste
We're going to talk a little bit about each other from here.
I'm going to ask you some questions, so don't think too much.
Let's answer in a quick tempo.
Yes, ma'am.
August 24th marks the 3rd anniversary since I joined the Halo Pro trainees.
What was the turning point moment for you in the past 3 years? The turning point moment for me in the past three years has been
Achieving my biggest goal in Halo Pro.
The public competency test for the Halo Pro trainees.
Mif, who had declared in June that she wouldn't buy any bombshells.
In fact, I secretly bought an item that I'd like to recommend to everyone
eyelash serum.
Today, August 21, is Perfect Day!
Mif's idea of a perfect idol is
Ms. Yoshikazu Miyamoto!
What do you keep in mind when singing a song?
Expressing my own personality.
How would you describe your role in JuiceJuice in one word?
I'm in charge of praising everyone.
Wow!
Thank you very much.
Now, let's see...
The moment when MIFF became a turning point for me was
It's called a competency test.
Why?
Well, something like that.
I took the test twice.
I received awards from Mr. Miyamoto and Mr. Ogata.
And I won the Best Performance Award.
I still have a lot of confidence in myself.
I feel that was a great turning point for me.
I saw it too.
I saw Miku singing “Sad Heaven”.
I also saw the video of Miku singing “Sad Heaven” and the video of her singing “Sad Heaven”.
It was an amazing song from then on.
It was a great song.
I got the impression that Miku must be a girl who likes to sing “Sad Heaven”, so it's a little strange that we're working together now.
And I heard that Mihu declared that she doesn't go shopping, and it's true that we go shopping together a lot, but I can't think of anything else.
I can only think of a few things I've seen her buy, among them eyelash serum.
But what about the shopping spree?
I'm not sure I even got the full length of your declaration that you don't get the blues.
I'm sure you've declared that you want to, but I'm sure you've been buying a lot of stuff.
I have the impression that he had set the lock screen of his cell phone to “I don't want to buy bombs”, but he didn't remember it at all, or he didn't think so.
I have a question for Ms. Matsunaga after the vtr. on Haloste.Questions for Ms. Matsunaga after vtr Haloste
Tsubaki Factory New Single Kodo OK
August 28 Onside
Tea Horse
Friends Exhibition Ties September 11 onsite
Hello Project New Member Audition 2024
Hello Project, now in its 27th year, is looking for new members!
Every member of Hello Project has experienced the same path.
It is an audition!
The important thing is to have the courage to take the first step.
We will do our best to support your first step!
This time, we will hold auditions in two categories
If you love singing, dancing, and Hello Project!
If you love Hello Project, you can audition in Hello Project category.
And if you want to show off your skills and personality in addition to singing and dancing, you can audition in the Hello Project category.
BEYOND THE POTENTIAL Division!
Why don't you join us and make your dream come true with Hello Project?
We are looking forward to hearing from you!
Haloste
Next, I would like to ask Ms. Matsunaga some questions.
I'll do my best.
Hello Project 2024 Summer All of Us is currently underway!
Please tell us some fun behind-the-scenes stories from this tour.
The intertwining of Mifu Kawashima and Hana Goto of Angulum!
The Hello Project New Member Audition 2024 is now open!
Do you have any impressive memories from the audition?
Singing and matching all the sides of a Rubik's Cube while demonstrating my special skills.
The first thing that comes to mind when I hear the word “summer memory” is
Summer festival
My most memorable memory of Kawashima Bijin is
Letters
Two months have passed since the new organization was formed.
What do you want to inject into JuiceJuice now?
A new way of thinking
Yes, thank you.
I'm going to keep digging into the questions that caught my attention.
What do you mean when you said that you put together a Rubik's Cube as one of your most memorable memories from the audition?
You sang Morning Musume's “Army of Love” while matching the sides of a Rubik's Cube. Singing Morning Musume's “Army of Love” while matching the faces of a Rubik's Cube.
Can you do it now?
That's amazing. I performed the trick of matching a single puzzle while singing and saying I've done it.
That was fun. Impressive.
Do you have any memories from the audition?
Yes I remember my audition, it was my last audition.
Hinoha Yoshida, the current Rosie Chronicle, was sitting alone on the couch.
I patted her on the head.
I said, “What's your name? And she told me her name.
And then she told me her name.
Where are you from? And everything.
We got to know each other, and we started practicing dancing together, and we ended up becoming trainees together.
And then we became trainees together, and now we have the same member color, and we debuted together, and we've been on the same stage, and we're really good friends.
I'm sure that you will have best friends and rivals too.
Hello Project is currently holding an audition for new members, and we are accepting applications until September 2nd.
I hope you can find your best friend with us!
I'm waiting!
I'll be waiting for you!
When I was asked “What is your best memory of Kawashima Bijin? I wrote “a letter” when I was asked “What is your favorite memory of Kawashima Bijin?
I have the impression that Mif and I had many opportunities to write letters to each other.
Last year, at Christmas time, we wrote to each other over the past year.
I found a letter on the street that said “You will receive a letter” and we wrote it to each other.
We wrote letters to each other.
Mif wrote me a letter on my birthday this year.
Mif wrote me a letter for my birthday this year, and she wrote a lot of things that made me very happy.
I treasure it now.
I used to read it before going to birthday events.
I think my memories are of the letters.
More to come after this episode of Halostei!
Please subscribe to our channel!
I'm Toa Makino, a 14-year-old junior high school student from Osaka.
My mom applied for the contest without my knowledge.
I didn't have many hobbies or special skills at that time.
So I decided to join the channel to gain confidence in myself.
I didn't really like singing at first.
I didn't know what to do.
But now I'm used to it and I can enjoy dancing and singing so much.
See you soon!See you then.
I love Gomato-san's Charbee Love!
This is Ms. Gomatsu.
I like Miki Fujimoto's way of thinking.
Maki Goto shines as a solo artist.
Maki Goto shines as a solo artist and stands out in the group.
I like Aya Matsuura because her singing voice makes me feel at home.
Writing essays and drawing pictures.
When the teacher asked me to write an essay
It took everyone else a long time to write it.
but I was able to do it quickly.
I got an “A” grade, so I thought maybe I'm good at writing.
It was an essay about what kind of time makes you happiest.
I wrote that I was happiest when I was having casual conversations with my friends.
When I was in elementary school.
I wrote an essay in elementary school, and it won a national competition and was displayed in many other places.
It was a work in which I painted butterflies, but everyone else had painted them colorful.
I wrote mine in black and brown, and it was well received.
People call me many different names, such as Toiwa-chan, Toiwa-jun, and Maki-no-Maki.
They say I talk a lot and laugh a lot.
I think I'm selfish and go my own way.
I do what I think at the time.
I sometimes act differently from everyone else.
I think I have my own pace.
I'm the one who talks all the time.
No one listens to me anymore.
I'm like a person who talks all the time by himself.
It's an ectopia.
It's a dimple.
It's right here.
I like basketball. I played in a club.
I like to work together with my team to score points. I like plums.
I've been eating them since I was a little kid, and I've always liked them. I like honey, shiso, all kinds of flavors.
I like them very sour rather than sweet.
I like light blue and recently fluorescent pink.
I like cats, dogs and ferrets.
I had a ferret when I was little.
I like cats and dogs because I have them now and they are very cute. I like cats and dogs because I have a cat and a dog now and they are so cute!
I have a toy poodle named Lulu and a toy poodle named Lulo.
They sleep together.
But sometimes I get tired of playing with them and get bored.
And then they turn the other way.
“Good night.
I think it's cute how they straddle the line and come back again.
I'd like to show the camera how I feel now.
First of all, I want to be able to sing and dance.
I want to be a person who can sing and dance, and I want to be able to do various things such as acting.
I want to become a person who can be active in any field.
Thank you for watching.
I wasn't really satisfied with the first one.
I wasn't satisfied with my first performance, but I think I grew more in the second performance than in the first.
I didn't win any awards.
I didn't win any prizes, but it made me want to try again.
I still can't get the rhythm of a detailed song.
I want to be able to listen to it and get it.
I will do my best in singing and dancing so that those who support me will be happy that they are supporting me.
Thank you for your support!
Thank you for watching!
Mif and I are both members of Juice Juice from the Halo Pro trainees.
I heard that the atmosphere of each generation of trainees is different.
When I was a trainee, the atmosphere was like survival in a good way.
There was a strong sense of rivalry among the trainees, and when we received the song assignments, we were the first to check them.
Whenever I received a song assignment, I was the first one to check it and see where my song assignment was.
It was amazing.
What was it like when you were a trainee?
When I first joined the company, I was really tense.
I would get on the bullet train every day and when I got to the station I would start to get nervous.
But at the end of the day, I was in the dressing room with Ayano Murakoshi of Rosy Chronicle, and we were playing YouTubers.
We played “YouTube” in the dressing room.
I still have that video, and I still have those memories.
But the episodes from the second part of the show, when I was a trainee at the Hallo Pro, gave me the impression that they were really good friends.
Please look forward to the next episode of Halo Pro Trainees Corner!
Haloste
Please look forward to the next episode of Halo Pro Trainee Corner!
With Ria Matsunaga of Juice Juice Riai Matsunaga of Juice Juice and
and Miho Kawashima of Juice Juice.
This is our first MC for Halostei, so we'd like to dig a little deeper into Miho.
We've asked some of the members and managers about Miho Kawashima's personality.
I'd like to introduce some of them to you.
Here are some episodes from the manager.
Unexpected side of Miho Kawashima
She may look quiet at a glance, but she is a talker and she and Matsunaga were singing and talking all the way to the shoot.
She really is a talker!
What do you think? What do you think of this unexpected side?
Huh? But I don't have that image of her.
The quiet side?
I don't get the impression that she's shy and talkative.
What? Yeah, I guess.
I think I talk a lot when I'm in a good mood.
I'm surprised that you didn't realize how talkative you are.
In the JuiceJuice dressing room, there's always the sound of MIF laughing or talking.
And I'm sure all the other members are too.
I think the first thing that comes to mind is that MIF is a chatterbox.
It's an aspect that is no longer surprising from the members' point of view, but at the beginning, she was really shy and catty.
I was very shy and cat-like at first, so when we talk alone, we talk about many things, but I wonder what kind of things we talk about.
When I'm with the members and we talk alone, we talk about the most trivial things, like how we're always joking around and how we're always talking about trivial things.
We talk about nothing at all, but when we're alone, we talk about the future.
But when we're alone, we talk about the future in a very serious way, and when we stay over together, we talk seriously until the morning.
When we stay together, we talk seriously about work and imagine the future together.
We also write about our future together.
I'll start with my impression of Mif.
I have the impression that Mif is very particular about what she does.
When we go to a sushi restaurant, she eats hamachi all the time.
She orders about 10 plates of hamachi and eats hamachi all the time.
I think he's very particular.
He is very particular.
I'm aware of it.
But eating the same thing all the time...
It's really funny.
It's funny.
It's funny.It's funny.
And there's something else that he's very particular about.
Other than sushi.
But for a long time
He's been doing that dance for a long time.
And...
The position of your hands, the position of your feet...
The angles...
I think it's partly because my mother told me so much at the time.
I've always been too particular about various people.
I've been told I'm too particular in both good and bad ways.
I think you're absolutely right.
That's true.
Haloste.
I'm going to tell you an episode that impressed me.
When Mifu was a guest at my birthday event.
She was on a very tight schedule and seemed very anxious.
But she practiced hard before the show and gave a wonderful performance.
I was really impressed by his hard work.
How was it?
Well, it was the first day of the tour, so it was like a rehearsal tour.
So I was really preoccupied, and I felt that I would rather attend other people's birthday events than my own birthday event.
I felt more responsible to attend other people's birthday events than my own, so I wondered if I could handle it.
That's why I've been wondering if I'm going to be okay.
So as I was practicing at night, I was wondering if I could handle it.
I called Mr. Matsunaga at night, right?
While I was crying.
Suddenly...
“I don't know if I can do it.
He called me in tears, saying he didn't know if he could do it.
But I told him to go to bed for now and that we would work together tomorrow.
It was a really great performance.
You were so cool!
Thank you so much!
It was great!
I was so anxious.
I tried really hard not to let my anxiety out on stage.
Now let me say hello again to you, the viewers of this show! Now, please say hello to all of you who are watching this show!
I'm sure there are many more concerts to come, including JuiceJuice's fall tour.
I'm sure there are many more concerts to come, but I'm going to enjoy each and every one of you at every concert with vigor.
I hope I can express myself in such a way that you will think of JuiceJuice as something you've never seen before.
I will do my best!
JuiceJuice
Diamond
me
ni
Diamond me ni
ni ni
ni
ni ni ni
ni ni ni ni
ni
ni ate
ni ni ni
hi me
rar
hu
aname
car CAR
I AM B e g e t h o u g h
em b e r e r e r e h
I want to live tonight
I wanna be you, I wanna be you, I wanna be you, I wanna be you, I wanna be you, I wanna be you
I want to be you, I want to sparkle
I want to be you, I want to bring out the best in you
Eva change
I'm so excited, I'm so lonely
Diamonds, Diamonds, Diamonds, Euro Heaven
Diamonds, diamonds, diamonds, diamonds, Euro Heaven
Let's dance together
I'm almost there, I'm almost there, I'm almost there, I'm almost there, I'm almost there.
With Juice Juice's A Tsunagari Ai
and Mif Kawashima of Juice Juice
It was time to say goodbye!
Mif, this is your first time to MC, how was it?
Yes, this is my first Haloste show.
I've been a member of Haloste
I've never seen a show called “Haloste” before. I wondered what it would be like when I saw the show.
I wondered how it would be like when I saw the schedule.
I was a little nervous when I saw the schedule.
But since it was my first time with Mr. Matsunaga
I felt very comfortable and had a lot of fun.
I never thought that I would be asked to be Mif's first MC.
I didn't expect to be Mif's first MC.
But I saw Mif read the script and worked hard on it, so I was happy to be able to MC with her.
I'm glad I was able to MC with her.
Here's an announcement.
Mif's favorite song
Hello Project 2024 Summer All of Us Regaaltael is now underway!
This weekend it will be performed in Shibuya, Tokyo!
If you are in the area, please come and see us!
JESJES Concert Tour 2024 Triangle Groove 2 will be held on
September 28th at the Honjo Bunka Hall of Global Software!
I still have no idea what kind of tour it will be, but
I'm really looking forward to seeing you all!
I am really looking forward to seeing you all! And.
Hello Project New Member Audition 2024 is now open! The deadline to apply is Monday, September 2nd at 10am!
We are looking forward to meeting the new you! Hello Project members will be appearing more and more on our channel.
New videos will be uploaded every Wednesday, so be sure to give us a high rating and subscribe to our channel!
This time it's Riai Matsunaga and Miho Kawashima from Juice Juice!
Good bye!